<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 16:44:59 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 16:44:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bird ringing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It was early one sunny Sunday morning when my Granny came to collect me to take me bird ringing with John Walsh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He had already put the nets up through the hedges at the top of the hill at Alder Carr Farm. We went bird ringing so early so the birds couldn’t see the net and they would fly straight into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First we went to look at the first net. There was a female and male Black Cap caught in the net. We walked back down to John’s van and
got a bit of string with the rings on and ringed the male black cap and weighed it and then let it go. After that we went for a walk to wait for the birds to fly into the nets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we had finished we went to look at another net and we found a Great Tit. This one had been ringed so we let it go. And we went to look at another net, in this one there was a very tangled Goldcrest. First John let me stroke it and it was very soft and we blew on it’s tummy to see if it was male or female. It was female because it had a breeding patch - a bald patch on their tummy. Then we let it go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/gold.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gold Creast&quot; title=&quot;Gold Creast&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/isaac-gold.resized.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gold Creast&quot; title=&quot;Gold Creast&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;Me with the Gold Creast.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a list of the other birds and plants I saw on my walk:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a Little Egret&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a Kestrel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;a Bee orchid&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;and a forget-me not&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bird ringing was really fun and I can’t wait to go again.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/birds/2016/07/03/bird-ringing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/birds/2016/07/03/bird-ringing.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>birds</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blue tit in the rain</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It was early in the morning and it was raining the worms had
started to come up, that only meant one thing: 
&lt;em&gt;that was birds&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of what I saw through the upstairs window this morning&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wren&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Starling&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Black bird&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;and a blue tit on a red hot pocker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/blue-tit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;blue tit&quot; title=&quot;Blue tit feeding on a red hot poker&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blue tit feeding on a red hot poker&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 16:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/birds/2016/06/23/blue-tit-in-garden.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/birds/2016/06/23/blue-tit-in-garden.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>birds</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My first blog post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is Isaac Sheldrake. I am 9 years old and have a real love for the environment. I especially like to search out small bugs and love to watch birds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I live on a farm so I have a great asortment of wildlife right on my door step. So what’s my plan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;To share with you all the amazing creatures that I see and tell you why they are incredible&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also think it’s important to let you know &lt;em&gt;how you can help&lt;/em&gt; all these creatures. As some of them are not doing too well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy my blog and if you’d like to get in touch please do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 21:06:54 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/awesomeness/2016/06/21/isaac-is-the-greatest.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/awesomeness/2016/06/21/isaac-is-the-greatest.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>awesomeness</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
